(An activity on his bucket list he dreamed of doing since his 20s)
(His last attempt at making his dream come true)
(I'm walking...)
(across the country.)
(He had always been disappointed that he couldn't complete it.)
(Then he had to say goodbye to his friend.)
(He decided to give it a try again.)
(Distance traveled)
(Distance traveled: 421km)
(17 days of traveling from Seoul to Gwangalli)
(Current location)
(On his last day, he only had 25km left.)
(He was running on fumes at this point.)
Hongga.
- He startled me. What? - His forehead...
Doesn't it look like a halo?
(He had a walking buddy who was much like an angel.)
(And he had another friend...)
(keeping him company during his travel.)
(When I looked at it, it gave me strength.)
(His last step to finish the walk)
(Let's go!)
(This is such a luxury for us.)
(This is the highlight of walking across the country.)
(I need to use the restroom.)
(It's on the border.)
(Come on. It's the stairs again.)
(The never-ending stairs)
(Oh, my legs...)
(Even my knees hurt.)
(To make it worse, it began pouring down.)
(Come on. What is that?)
(It's not a hill. It's a mountain.)
(Staggering)
(Why did I ever decide to walk across the country?)
(16 nights and 17 days, distance traveled: 432km)
Okay.
I made it all the way here.
I can't let this...
(Groaning)
I'm almost there.
It goes for all cars. If you take a break in first gear,
it's hard to go up the hill.
- Right. - That's...
- They would roll back. - Yes, they'd roll backward.
(Screaming)
(Grunting)
You can't do this alone.
They got each other.
He would've given up long ago if he were alone.
Ta-da.
(He finally reaches the top.)
(Groaning)
(Exhaling)
(Spacing out)
That's how I felt exactly when Baengnokdam came into view.
(That's how I felt exactly when Baengnokdam came into view.)
You're bringing up Mount Halla again?
Let me explain. That was the toughest moment for me.
You went there four years ago.
- It was four years ago? - Yes.
- Hyun Moo, then... - I mentioned it 40 times.
(This is his 41st time mentioning his hike to Baengnokdam.)
You're so cool. Happy New Year.
(Baengnokdam is the best.)
(Panting)
Let's go.
(They set out again after catching their breath.)
(Gwangalli Beach, Busan)
You're halfway there.
(Distance traveled: 12km Distance remaining: 13km)
Is it raining?
I think it's hailing.
Come on. Even the weather is killing me.
How nice.
(Clenching his teeth)
(The storm is getting stronger.)
(The two of them are getting soaked in the rain and the wind.)
Oh, no. What a tough time they're having.
(The bad weather is tiring him out little by little.)
Actor Ku. I'm a fan.
(Actor Ku. I'm a fan.)
I saw you walking by earlier, so I bought this for you.
I'm about to tear up now.
- My gosh. I would tear up too. - I'd be so grateful too.
I want to give you a hug.
- But I'm wet. - I'm a huge fan.
- Thank you. - I'll keep supporting you.
- Have a good day. - Thank you.
I'll enjoy this too.
(Touched)
- My gosh. - I'd be so grateful.
He saw me from afar.
- And he bought me coffee. - My gosh.
- He followed you after buying it. - Yes, he did.
- That's such a kind gesture. - That's so touching.
I'm so grateful.
Holding this coffee is keeping me warm.
(Precious)
I guess it was cold.
You know what?
You barely stand out in this episode.
He's so eye-catching.
(A scene-stealer)
(Thanks to the warm coffee,)
(the two of them continue walking.)
We walked over 10km now, right?
(Swinging)
We walked 13.5km.
You guys came a long way.
We're past our halfway point.
(Distance traveled: 13.5km Distance remaining: 11.5km)
Seriously.
(He's so close to completing his grand journey of 446km.)
I'm so close.
My gosh, 16 nights and 17 days.
It must feel like it's been a month.
(Struggling)
(Groaning)
(Limping)
(It seems something's wrong with him.)
(His face begins to stiffen.)
(Sighing)
Gosh, my calves are killing me.
Come on.
Oh, my back.
(Worried)
Okay. Let's keep going. We're very close.
Okay.
- We can do it. - We can do it.
Getting this far wasn't easy.
Right. It wasn't easy.
To be honest, I felt really bad for Hongga.
I couldn't keep up with his pace.
My gosh.
(Let me man up and keep going.)
You're even clenching your teeth.
It was really difficult for you to keep walking at that point.
Didn't seeing cars speed by make you want to get in one?
I didn't think about that.
My goal was to walk 446km.
If I were to get on the wheels even for 10m,
it would make me feel my whole journey was fake.
- It would negate the whole purpose. - It would.
I bet you felt more like that since it was your last day.
That's why when people saw me on the street,
they asked me if I wanted a ride.
- A lot of people offered. - Really?
If I took the offer, this would be meaningless.
- The whole thing would be fake. - That's right. So I said no.
It was a challenge against yourself and a promise at the same time.
Right.
Hey, it's raining quite a lot.
- We should take shelter... - Yes.
- under a roof when we see one. - Okay.
- I need to check on my feet too. - Okay.
It must've been harder since the weather was bad.
When my shoes got wet, my feet kept sliding in them.
That would cause more blisters.
Right here. There's a gazebo.
Hey. My gosh. That's the perfect spot.
- Let's take a test here. - I love it.
(Regrouping for a moment to avoid the rain)
Wait, it's a cat.
(Groaning)
How can he not grunt?
Lie down for a bit.
I should check on them.
Putting on wet shoes again would be tough.
I don't think you can ever throw out those shoes.
- Never. - Right?
(Lying down)
My goodness.
Oh, my. Lying down on the gazebo...
Shouldn't we have reached Gwangalli at this rate?
My calves are killing me.
(The journey of 446km doesn't seem to end.)
Check on your toes. See if they're okay.
He barely talked on the way.
- I started to get worried. Yes. - It made you worry.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Right here too.
(His blistered foot got soaked in the rain.)
- My gosh. - He stuck a thread in there.
(Shutting his eyes)
Hey. Doesn't that hurt?
Hongga's feet were in worse shape than mine.
- But he didn't say a thing. - Right.
The blister kept getting popped inside his shoe.
That guy, Hongga, is amazing.
- He didn't show it at all. - Right.
- He's such a cool guy. - He didn't show it.
He's an amazing guy.
My foot...
(Looking clean)
It looks fine.
My body itself is super strong.
(Laughing)
Hey. I practically have baby feet.
I have the feet of an infant. I have baby feet.
So your frame is fine. But the engine must be rotting.
Comparing it to a car... Hey, it's not rotting.
(Rustling)
Hey, you're addicted. You finished the whole bag of seasoned salt.
That was a fresh bag.
- No, this is... - Hey.
(Grabbing)
That's all you have left from this 250g bag. This is crazy.
That's why you can't sleep and keep going to the bathroom at night.
I'm telling you. This is very effective.
(Shaking)
Hey.
- Hey. - Oh, no. Sir.
Sir.
(Gulping it down)
I feel so refreshed with some salt.
That's true, though.
Some salt definitely refreshed you.
Hey, let me take some too.
(Let me try some salt too.)
It's like taking a tequila shot.
You took too much.
Hear me out. The salt hits you so aggressively.
I get why you keep taking it.
I almost finished it.
Right. You almost finished it.
(He finished a whole bag of seasoned salt.)
- Is it different salt? - A lot of people participating...
in triathlons and marathons...
- do eat salt. - People eat salt during marathons.
- But they don't take seasoned salt. - Here's why.
We both have this in common. We have the palate of a kid.
So it has to be tasty.
(Laughing)
Okay.
(After a seasoned-salt refresher...)
Are your legs okay?
Let's get going. We're very close.
Yes.
(They set out again with the energy from seasoned salt.)
My gosh, this is so nice.
We're getting so close.
(This is great.)
Let's keep going.
(After a short break...)
- That was a great energy boost. - We're very close.
(Walking over a puddle)
After a trip like that, I bet you'd know all the regions by heart.
Gosh, no. I didn't even know...
- where I was going, to be honest. - Really? You can't even remember?
- I was just walking mindlessly. - Because it was really tough?
I'm feeling a bit more energy now that we're getting close.
Stay strong, Power Ku
Let's keep at it.
(Frowning)
What happened?
(Looking fatigued)
Gosh, why is it raining so much? Oh, no.
- Hey, it's raining way too hard. - Oh, my.
It's pouring down.
All right. Let's keep a positive mindset.
Okay.
Let's only think about Gwangalli. Come on.
It's raining too hard.
And it's super windy too.
(They can't keep their eyes open due to the strong wind and rain.)
- For goodness' sake. - My goodness.
My gosh. It's windy and raining.
Oh, my. I guess...
this year will be full of happy occasions.
Actually, if we had good weather today,
it wouldn't be that memorable.
- Right. That will be memorable. - And...
- Hard times are more memorable. - That's right.
(He keeps telling himself positive things.)
(Trudging along)
He's limping.
(Despite his positive mindset, his legs are tired.)
(Glancing)
- How long do we have left? - From here?
- About 8.5km. - About 8.5km.
Then we have only two hours to go.
(Distance traveled: 16.5km Distance remaining: 8.5km)
(16 nights, 17 days, distance traveled: 437.5km)
My gosh. Seriously.
- Gosh, the backpack must be heavy. - It must be.
Actually, walking 25km in 1 day isn't that bad...
out of all the days we walked so far.
- But you did that day after day. - Right.
- That's right. - Going to a supermarket is tough...
- when it rains that hard. - Right.
I couldn't see ahead and because of the wind,
the resistance made it harder to walk.
(My gosh, this isn't easy.)
Lean over there.
(Leaning against the telephone pole)
This is crazy.
(They lean their body while waiting for the signal.)
You must want to lean on anything you see.
I rarely lean on the poles when it rains.
- Right. - Because of electric shocks.
I hate jeopardizing my safety.
- Just in case? - Just in case.
But I didn't care about that then.
(Walking through the heavy rain pouring down on him)
(They force themselves to keep walking.)
I don't think I can do that.
(Amazed)
I want to rest.
Gosh, we made it to Beomil-dong.
- Gosh. - Are you almost there?
We're here. We're so close to finishing it.
(Let's keep walking a little bit more.)
(Closing his eyes)
You guys stopped talking.
We just sat down without saying a thing.
(They quietly plop down on the bench.)
(They're walking without saying a thing to each other.)
(Then they rest for a bit.)
- Oh, no. - My gosh.
(Heartbroken)
My gosh. Come on.
(When on earth will we get to finish this journey?)
There's a pattern.
We start off by telling each other supportive things. "Good job."
"Let's go there tomorrow."
But the thing is, after the third day,
- we didn't have much to talk about. - Right.
It took a toll on us physically.
(The harder it got, the quieter they got.)
Because of that, when it got quiet, I had all kinds of thoughts.
One of the thoughts would be,
"What's the point of doing this?"
"No one will give me credit for it."
"This won't get me an award or anything."
(This won't get me an award or anything.)
These thoughts kept bothering me and made me want to give up.
- You had a lot on your mind. - But...
the hardest moment for me was...
"Why am I so weak?"
"I used to be so positive. Why am I so weak-minded?"
Despite all that, I didn't give up...
because it might haunt me.
The failed attempt in my 20s kept haunting me.
I couldn't finish the walk...
because the bottoms of my feet were killing me.
Whenever bad things happened to me,
I thought, "That makes sense. I gave up..."
"so easily that time."
"So whenever things got tough,"
"I just wanted to give up." I thought about giving up first.
I was trying to put an end to that with this journey.
That was why.
That pushed me to challenge myself.
- This journey had several purposes. - Yes.
I wanted to achieve a lot with this journey.
(That's why I can't give up.)
I thought, "Let's take one step at a time."
(He simply continues walking one step at a time.)
I kept trying to be grateful.
(He remembered...)
(many grateful moments from his 17-day journey.)
(Like a mom...)
(and a friend, they gave him strength to keep going.)
- I'm about to tear up now. - Thank you.
(Thank you.)
(And...)
(he also had a partner who walked by his side.)
(Out of gratitude for everyone's support...)
Gosh, it's cold.
- I just kept going. I just did it. - Right.
- That's the spirit. - Yes.
(Breathing out)
I can see my breath when it's April now.
It was 8°C that day.
- The temperature dropped a lot. - It must've been freezing.
- It was cold. - You kept walking in the rain.
- We kept walking in the rain. - Yes.
(Gwangalli Beach)
(Distance traveled: 20.5km Distance remaining: 4.5km)
(Glancing)
Hey, look.
(He spots something and goes straight to it.)
Hello.
- Can I get a haircut? - Sure.
- What? - That was random.
I'm sorry. But we're wet from the rain.
- Sure. It's okay. - Okay.
That was so random.
It's the same for me and Hongga.
We wanted to reset...
our mindset.
I wanted to change everything and start fresh.
I was sweating so much when I was walking.
We talked about it and decided to get a haircut...
toward the end when we were close to finishing it.
The way you embrace the end is really important.
- Yes. That's why we decided on it. - You know? Right.
That's really cool.
(They enter a barbershop for a new haircut and mindset.)
- How short do you want it? - I want a 6mm buzz cut.
That's pretty short.
Look at his forehead. It's so embarrassing.
Oh, no.
(The tan line is very visible.)
You should've gone to a tanning salon first.
A 6mm buzz cut. Okay.
I'll go right ahead.
- Wait. - What is it?
- Wait. - Yes?
What is it?
Let's go with a 1mm buzz cut.
- A 1mm buzz cut? - Yes.
- What? - What?
Monks usually get a 1mm buzz cut.
A 1mm buzz cut?
I got a 1mm buzz cut when I enlisted in the army.
I was so shocked.
A 1mm buzz cut?
I would have to shave his head then.
Let's just do it. I want a new mindset.
I want to start fresh.
- A 1mm buzz cut? Are you sure? - Yes. Let's go with that.
(What's gotten into him?)
- My gosh. - That will be really short.
That sounds better.
He asked for the haircut with...
- A reverent heart? - a reverent heart.
So our journey wasn't over yet.
But we were getting close. It felt so weird.
I bet.
(He's refocusing himself as the end is near.)
(Looking serious)
You can't change your mind now.
- Is this how short you want it? - Yes.
- I could understand him, though. - Do you like it?
- I think I get it too. - It's like being reborn.
- He needed a turning point too. - That was precisely it.
Yes, that's right.
(His hair is getting shorter.)
Gosh, this guy...
- He's getting ready for it too. - Totally.
(His determination to complete the walk is getting stronger.)
(He gets a haircut with a sense of reverence.)
- He looks better with this haircut. - He looks cool.
- He has a beautiful head. - Yes.
This is crazy.
- Should I sit down now? - Sure.
- You should shave your head too. - I...
My hair is pretty long now.
- Okay. - So I want...
this haircut.
- What is it? - What are you showing her?
- Okay. - So I want this haircut.
- Wait. That's Lee Je Hoon. - You showed her Lee Je Hoon?
Hear me out. It's...
(He shows her the hairstyle he wants before the haircut.)
- So I want this haircut. - What is it?
- Wait. That's Lee Je Hoon. - You showed her Lee Je Hoon?
Hear me out. It's... What was it called?
- It's called a double haircut. - A double haircut?
- A two-block... What was it? - Isn't that a wolf cut hairstyle?
- A wolf cut! - A wolf cut.
- I hear that's trending these days. - A wolf cut.
- That's... - It's trending now?
- It was trendy 25 years ago. - Or in the early 2000s.
- Really? It's not trendy now? - No.
What are you talking about?
(This is all new to them.)
- Could you cut the side? - Just the side?
My bangs are long too.
I want my bangs to be this short.
This is the overall vibe I want.
I want Woo Seok's haircut.
Do you know Woo Seok?
Well,
we were in the same news articles about four years ago.
News articles?
Reporters published articles saying our era was coming.
They really wrote that?
- Yes. I took many screenshots. - Maybe they made a mistake.
No. There were many news articles about that.
I hear fake news has been spreading a lot.
I love you, Woo Seok.
I'm following your career too.
I believe in your sense of style too.
I saw you cutting his hair. And I knew you were good.
I believe in her.
(She finally starts working on his hair...)
(after a long explanation.)
You look slimmer than I expected. Did you lose a lot of weight?
We walked here all the way from Seoul.
- I started walking from my house. - So you lost a lot of weight.
Right. I lost weight.
(So I'll try wearing Je Hoon's and Woo Seok's hairstyle.)
Don't I look cute in person?
I look cuter in person than on TV, right?
You're fishing for an answer.
- You're not answering me. - You do.
- He's forcing her to answer him. - No.
(Sung Hwan wants to chat.)
(Moving around)
He's doing something.
(Meanwhile, he's done shaving his beard.)
- Oh, my goodness! - He also shaved his beard?
He also has a tan line on his chin.
Right. That's where his beard was.
(Just like his forehead, his beard line is white.)
I thought he was an angel.
I hope someone publishes Hongga-themed emoticons.
- I think someone will. - I think so too.
(Emoticons you want to own)
- That's crazy. - No one can beat that.
He looks like a baby now.
- Right. He has a baby face. - Let me see.
(Hongga's face looks even smoother without the beard.)
Seriously. I've never seen you without your beard.
I think it's been a decade since I last shaved.
Even I feel awkward looking at myself.
Gosh, you don't look like yourself.
But that was a big decision for him.
Shaving your ten-year-old beard couldn't have been an easy decision.
Right.
(She starts cutting off Sung Hwan's hair too.)
She's snipping it away.
That must give him some energy, though.
Right. It felt so weird. I'm serious.
- Here it goes. - Go for it.
(As determined as he is,)
(he decides to cut his hair quite short on the sides.)
(Letting out a sigh)
That must feel weird indeed.
(In no time, she's almost done.)
- I love it. - You do?
- I love it. - Wait.
People might believe me if I say I'm in high school.
You do look young.
- That's it. - Thank you.
(He has gotten younger in a flash.)
My gosh. This is the haircut I wanted.
There's Lee Je Hoon.
I really love it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Good luck. Bye. - Okay.
Thank you.
My gosh, let's get going.
This is our last day.
(Resolute)
(Meanwhile, the raindrops have grown bigger.)
(They slowly push through the heavy rain.)
Gosh, it's cold.
It's freezing.
(Exhaling)
- Oh, no. He's so freezing. - He's shaking.
- This is so cold. - Is it hypothermia?
Raindrops kept seeping into my jacket.
I had hypothermia.
- You didn't have extra clothes. - Yes.
(Pulling it out)
(He unties it from his wrist.)
(He tightly grabs Kkotbun's leash in his hand.)
(Exhausted)
We can't be late.
We must get there no matter what.
I'll get there even if it kills me.
Let's go.
(They continue on the walk without a break.)
- I really hate the rain. - Right.
They would already have arrived if it hadn't rained.
- Right. - If it hadn't rained.
We have 3.9km left.
So 59 minutes... We have 1 hour... No, we can be there in 59 minutes.
Okay.
(They're not even an hour away from their destination.)
Hongga.
- If we say it's good... - It's good.
- If we say we can do it... - We can!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(They shout out the slogan with the last ounce of their energy.)
(Distance remaining)
They used up their energy a long time ago, seriously.
- They did. Right. - Willpower is keeping them going.
- They're walking with willpower. - It's all in their willpower.
(It's already 6:15pm.)
(Glancing up)
You know what? We've been walking for a while.
How come there's no sign for the beach?
- That's so painful. - Seeing the sign...
for the Gwangalli Beach would give us some energy.
- But we couldn't see it. - The sun is going down too.
(The signs are nowhere to be seen.)
(Grabbing)
(The pain has spread up to his thighs now.)
(Limping)
It's...
pouring rain.
(As they get closer to the destination,)
(it rains more heavily.)
- The weather really isn't helping. - I know.
It was so nice in the morning.
(It rains more heavily.)
My legs...
aren't moving properly now.
(As pain intensifies over time,)
(he can't help but grimace.)
We're nearly there.
We've walked 443km so far. Only 3km remain now.
Only 3km.
By myself,
I would've never succeeded in this.
Thank you so much, Hongga.
- Hongga is so dependable. - It's really exhausting.
- Without Hongga, - My legs hurt so much.
I would've failed.
(I wouldn't have gotten far.)
Still,
(They rely on each other...)
the end is near.
(and move forward one step at a time.)
(Staring)
What? Hey! I can see it!
(What? Hey! I can see it!)
- What? - Gwangalli. I can see it.
(Gwangalli!)
At that moment...
Gwangalli.
(A road sign for Gwangalli finally shows itself.)
We just need to go a bit further.
It's 1.9km away.
(Finally, the end is right before their eyes.)
It'll take less than 30 minutes.
(However, they halt after a short while.)
(Squeezing his eyes shut)
(The pain in his legs keeps getting worse.)
It hurts again.
(His body is long past its limits.)
It hurts when I lift my foot.
This is driving me crazy.
For goodness' sake.
(Exhausted)
(Once more, he thinks about...)
(the meaning of this moment.)
At that point,
my back and feet were in bad shape.
I know how bad Sung Hwan's joints are.
- Right. - It's a miracle he went that far.
So I held it even more tightly...
at that point.
(He holds it in his hand as tightly as ever...)
(and walks toward the Gwangalli Beach.)
We have 700m left. We have 10 minutes left.
The end is near. That news will energize them.
(My goodness)
(Gosh)
At the end of the road,
I see the sea.
- The sea. - The sea.
The sea is at the end of the road.
(From a distance, they see a glimpse of the Gwangalli Beach.)
Seriously.
After the crosswalk,
we'll reach the sea.
(Well...)
I choked up a bit.
In the past, as I walked for 17 days,
I experienced so many things.
The memories flitted through my mind as if I was watching a movie.
(The memories flitted through his mind.)
(From Seoul to Busan)
My condition on the first day...
(16 nights...)
(and 17 days)
(Total distance traveled:)
(446km)
(And the last step of the journey)
Let's go over there.
(They finally set their feet...)
(on the Gwangalli Beach.)
- Impressive. - They did it.
Honestly, they're incredible.
(He can't believe...)
(that this is the end of their long journey.)
We're here.
(Final destination)
(They arrive at the Gwangalli Beach.)
We're here.
(Slowly, he checks out...)
(the sea at Gwangalli.)
(We're actually here.)
(Rummaging)
You know,
after that day,
I haven't watched them once.
(You know, after that day, I haven't watched them once.)
I'm talking about the videos.
(I'm talking about the videos.)
Did you reach the other side?
(Did you reach the other side?)
See you later. Later.
(See you later.)
Have fun...
(Have fun...)
with your friends.
(with your friends.)
Now that it's over, my heart feels lighter.
I wanted to do...
the cross-country trip with her.
(I wanted to do the cross-country trip with her.)
I didn't know that I'd get so emotional.
But...
for a second,
(But for a second...)
I looked at the beach and...
(I looked at the beach and...)
The place where we played together...
was right next to me.
(Their precious memories...)
(revisit him at the Gwangalli Beach.)
When I saw the place,
the emotions that had piled up...
for two months after her passing...
(The emotions that had piled up for two months after her passing)
got relieved. That was why I cried.
I'm not depressed or anything.
I can't hold on to these emotions throughout my life.
But because of the happy memories,
(It's just that they're my happy memories.)
I shed tears without even realizing it.
(The time they spent together)
Did you sleep well?
(The place they shared)
(Longing fills the empty spots.)
There is one thing that makes me feel good.
Over the course of 17 days,
I kept my promise to Kkotbun.
I promised her a cross-country trip.
We went to Gangwon Province, Jeolla Province,
Busan, and North Gyeongsang Province.
(He promised Kkotbun a cross-country trip.)
Let's go. Come here.
Because of that, my heart is lighter.
(Since he kept his promise today, his heart is lighter.)
Now, I can say Kkotbun's name out loud.
I must be a really positive person.
I've become a lot better.
This is the day...
I'll remember until the end of time.
It's the memory I'll hold onto for the rest of my life.
(It's the memory I'll hold onto for the rest of my life.)
My goodness.
Many people were worried about me.
But she has become a good memory in my heart. I'm thankful for that.
This is what I realized while doing the cross-country walk.
On some days, the weather was nice.
On other days, the weather was bad.
When it rains, you can brave it and walk forward.
When it hails, you can brave it and walk forward.
- You just need to keep going. - I had that thought.
That's one lesson I learned.
You just need to keep going.
I learned that.
Now, I have the strength to start anew.
- Yes. - You'll advance forward.
That's right. That was the meaning behind my tears.
I felt many emotions.
- I've experienced pet loss. - Yes.
Actually, this is my first time talking about it.
I got to make some last memories with Toto, right?
Toto passed a week after that.
I feel like Toto was at the end of her life.
- To spend the last week with me, - That's right.
she mustered up the energy.
- That's right. - She passed the very next week.
(She mustered up the energy.)
(With all her might,)
(Toto gifted him the last moment of her life.)
My dog did the same.
- Right? - About a week or ten days prior,
I wondered how she had become so healthy.
- She could go on walks. - Right.
But she passed soon afterward.
- I feel like they wait for you. - They wait for you.
- They give us time to prepare. - That's right.
- That's right. - She'll keep giving you strength.
Sung Hwan, as you live your life,
- you'll keep remembering her. - Of course. It goes without saying.
- You'll think of her at times. - Of course.
And there must be many people who are experiencing...
pet lost.
And there must be many people who are experiencing pet lost.
- I just think... - It's "Pet loss."
- Pet loss. - Pet loss.
Pet loss.
- My goodness. - "Lost?"
- I lost the urge to cry. - Seriously.
- That's good. - Sung Hwan, I lost the urge to cry.
I was about to cry.
(His tears are lost.)
It's "Pet loss."
There must be many people who are experiencing pet loss.
I almost burst out laughing.
I think it's important to overcome it in your own way,
- That's right. - albeit slowly.
- Keep your mental state healthy. - That's right.
- We'll meet in the end. - Are you doing well?
We'll meet only after 40 years.
I'll stay healthy.
- Kkotbun will want that. - That's right.
- That's right. - Yes.
(Sobbing uncontrollably)
(He can't calm his emotions.)
Hongga, you went through a lot.
(Hongga, you went through a lot.)
(Weeping)
(Glancing over)
- Why is he... - My goodness.
- I mean... - This is embarrassing.
- While I'm thankful... - He is crying too hard.
Is he crying over his bad haircut?
- Did he look in the mirror? - It's for his lost mustache.
- I thought you were crying. - Oh, my.
- I thought the same. - Sung Hwan's mouth was closed,
but I heard the sobbing noises.
I wondered where they were coming from.
If you aren't the type to cry a lot,
- it can be an outburst. - That's right.
He is the type to smile all the time.
He is having an emotional outburst.
Hongga, stop crying.
(Weeping)
Let's have a can of beer.
- Finally. - Drink.
It was our promise.
Here.
Cheers.
(Cheers)
(Weeping)
(Gulping)
(Glancing over)
You know...
He can drink right after crying.
- Seriously. - It's a bit surprising.
(He replenishes the body water he has lost by crying.)
(He downs beer after 17 days.)
A truly romantic experience is...
walking all the way to Busan.
My goodness.
(I'll let myself go.)
You have my respect. Seriously, you have my respect.
It's the epitome of romance.
When else would you lie on a beach?
(That's right. This is romance.)
It was a nice trip.
(Forever...)
(in My Heart)
(I Live Alone)
Welcome.
It's back once again.
Introducing the Rainbow Friends,
IRF, Part Six.
Whose friend will we see today?
Today, we'll see my friend.
- Who is it? - Introducing Bae Na Ra's Friend.
- Really? - It's IBF.
- IBF. - IBF.
He is a charming man who shines in every work...
with his unrivaled character, Actor Yu Su Bin.
Yu Su Bin.
- Welcome. - Hello.
(Welcome.)
(The fun and trustworthy secretary of "Perfect Crown")
(He has made himself known in every work...)
(such as "Weak Hero Class 2" and "Crash Landing on You.")
(The irreplaceable actor, Yu Su Bin)
(Very nervous)
- Sit in the middle. - Come this way.
They're actually friends.
It has been a while.
It's good to have you here.
(Glancing down)
They're so happy to see each other.
- It has been a while. - Gosh.
- What are you doing? - The zipper was a bit down.
I saved you.
- My goodness. - Hold on.
It was a bit down.
- Thank you. - Okay.
Su Bin,
please say hello to the viewers of I Live Alone.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Actor Yu Su Bin. I'm in your care.
How do you know Na Ra?
We were both in "Weak Hero Class 2..."
and "Tastefully Yours."
What's the age difference?
- Na Ra is a year older than me. - He is a year older than you.
We go on trips together.
- Are you guys that close? - Yes.
Su Bin takes good care of people around him.
He is very considerate.
I wanted to introduce this charming friend,
so I invited him here.
- You know, I got... - Thank you.
a text from IU about your visit to the show.
Really?
She asked me to take good care of you...
because you were a kind and talented actor.
We'll see how kind you are.
I'm not that kind.
- Really? - I'm a bad man.
(Bad Man)
(It's pitch black inside the room.)
It's pitch black.
(Embarrassed)
(He is sleeping soundly in the dark room.)
(Moving)
(Lifting his arms)
(He wakes up without an alarm.)
Hello,
I'm in my sixth year of living alone.
I'm Actor Yu Su Bin. It's nice to meet you.
(Making a V-sign)
(Rustling)
What?
- Is it a tablet PC? - A tablet PC stand?
(He turns on his tablet PC upon walking up.)
It's "Infinite Challenge."
(He begins his morning with "Infinite Challenge.")
He changed the angle to watch it while lying on his side.
I can tell from the angle that he is used to this.
He took the added height from the pillow...
- into consideration. - Yes. You're precisely right.
(The best angle that took the pillow into consideration)
(Comfortable)
(Turning over)
(He takes something that was right next to him.)
It's better to do that.
I have it too. It's a massage pillow.
(This time as well, he stretches out his arm from his bed...)
(and puts on the heated eye mask.)
Do you use such eye masks at home?
I use it because I get a sty often.
I heard that applying warmth to the eye area...
- could remove inflammation. - That's right.
- That's right. - So I do that in the morning.
(That's enough.)
(While lying down, he switches to another pillow.)
(He hugs the pillows comfortably.)
- He is watching two things. - Two.
(He's focused on his tablet PC and phone at the same time.)
- Is he playing a video game? - Yes. I'm playing a video game.
I'm playing a soccer game.
I reached the top five in Korea.
- Gosh! - Really?
(With his two monitors,)
(his happiness doubles.)
(He chuckles for a while in the same spot.)
He keeps doing everything on his bed.
He didn't touch the ground.
- Everything is... - Right.
within reach.
- I'm very lazy. - Right.
I don't like moving around a lot.
People in the future might end up living like that.
- In the future. - Right.
(He's still on his bed.)
He got up.
(He preciously picks up his tablet PC...)
(which he was watching "Infinite Challenge" with.)
(Bringing down)
(He finally takes his first step on the floor!)
(With his glorious steps,)
(he moves right next to the bed.)
What was that?
- He moved right there? - It's a treadmill.
I would get too lazy if it's in the living room.
I placed it there so that I can use it...
- Awesome. - as soon as I get up.
You never use it when it's placed in the living room.
- Never. - Right.
Right. Even when you get changed,
you think about giving up around three times.
That was why I placed my clothes there.
- Awesome. - So I can run right away.
- To prevent avoiding it? - Right.
(Shall I start my morning workout?)
He's running right after waking up.
(Reaching)
(He puts on the socks he placed on the treadmill.)
(He puts on his shorts right away as well.)
(Rummaging)
(Did he wrap his ear with a rubber band?)
- The rubber band. - Idol stars use that method.
- The ear crushing? - It's to reduce the swelling.
- Because of the swelling. - Right.
My face swells up so much.
I always do it for around 30 minutes in the morning.
(He picks up the shoes placed on the treadmill.)
(He picks up his headphones.)
(He also picks up his knee pads.)
(He gets himself fully ready inside his room.)
(Shall I begin?)
(He brings up the incline to the highest point.)
So you focus on the incline instead of the speed.
I feel a bit hesitant to bring up the speed at home.
That's why I bring up the incline as much as possible.
- You focus on the incline. - You bring it up.
(He does a power walk in his room.)
He keeps watching "Infinite Challenge."
"Infinite Challenge" is the only show I watch.
I watch the same episodes over and over.
There's a sense of peace that "Infinite Challenge" brings.
(You're right.)
(Laughing)
(He laughs even during his workout.)
(His steps feel brighter thanks to "Infinite Challenge.")
Some people won't use it even if it's by their bed.
- Right. - It's amazing that he's using it.
- He's never lazy. - Right.
(Is the lazy one actually diligent?)
(He has been working out for 30 minutes already.)
(Let's do a bit more.)
(His ears have already turned dark blue.)
(He covers them with his headphones.)
(He carries on with his fun workout.)
(Laughing)
(After laughing and walking for a while...)
- He's sweating. - He's sweating.
(He's drenched in sweat.)
(Turning it off)
(I completed another course today.)
(His 45-minute morning workout comes to an end.)
I had a weak immune system.
It got much stronger after I started with this workout.
- Your immune system? - Right.
(After taking special care of his immune system and tablet PC,)
(he heads out of his room.)
Oh, yes!
His house looks neat.
(Welcome to Su Bin's house.)
I currently live in Jeungsan-dong.
I pay monthly rent.
Jeungsan? Is that in Ilsan?
No. It's right by here. Jeungsan-dong.
I see. Right by here?
My drama or movie shoots...
were usually held in the Paju or Yeoncheon area.
I struggle to wake up in the morning.
To secure as much sleep as possible,
I ended up finding this area.
(Among the neat interior design,)
(a lot of his laundry and things are hidden in the balcony.)
It doesn't seem like he's interested in decorating his house.
(The tableware is placed randomly.)
(The master bedroom with the treadmill...)
(is filled with scripts and his acting notes.)
("No Longer Human")
"No Longer Human" is a great one.
("Weak Hero Class 2")
(He cherishes the moments he spent with Na Ra.)
(Su Bin comes out to the living room after his workout.)
(Opening)
(He takes out an aluminum pot from the cupboard.)
(He places it on the burner after filling it with water.)
That gets the water boiled the fastest.
Is he making ramyeon?
(Let's see.)
(He takes out a mysterious sheet from the cupboard.)
Tea?
(He places it on the cup.)
- It's decaf coffee. - I see. It's coffee.
- It's a drip bag. - Right.
(Being careful)
(He scoops out the ground coffee beans.)
You're not using the coffee machine.
Right. I have to put in the capsule and water.
- I found myself avoiding it. - Were you too lazy to use it?
I only used it around two times.
The drip bag is a lot more convenient to use.
The used bag just needs to be thrown out.
- Those are blueberries. - Blueberries?
Blueberries are really good for the immune system.
Honey.
(It's ready after a good stir.)
Right.
(He puts on his oven mitts.)
(He grabs the pot with the boiled water.)
(He pours the water from the pot.)
(He moves the pot with boiled water carefully.)
Check out his face.
I should get him an electric kettle.
(He keeps a distance as the water might splash on him.)
(Drip coffee is made by slowly pouring water from a kettle.)
(He uses an aluminum pot with boiled water instead.)
(As the coffee is slowly being made,)
(he washes an apple.)
He eats really healthy.
I suffered a lot with shingles.
You must have an issue with your immune system.
Right.
That is why I'm trying my best to eat healthy.
- What is that? - What is that?
(Using all his strength)
That's an apple cutter.
I have that as well.
- It gets cut at once like that. - That's nice.
The seeds are left out like that.
The part with the seeds becomes a tube.
You just need to throw that out.
- That's nice. - That's really nice.
- You saw it on social media, right? - I did!
I bought it right away after seeing the ad.
I have that and also the watermelon cutter.
The watermelon is cut like this as well.
There's one for watermelons as well?
- There's such a thing? - It gets done at once!
It's as big as a steering wheel.
Does it require a lot of strength?
When you press down, it spreads out like this.
- Gosh. - You can eat it right away.
He buys all sorts of things.
- It must be helpful in the summer. - It will take so long without it.
(He checks if the coffee is made well.)
(Falling in)
That always does that.
Why does it do that?
You aren't supposed to stir it.
The water shouldn't be poured at once.
- That always happens to me as well. - You take turns to pour the water.
It also feels nice with the ground coffee beans.
(What do I do?)
(He puts his finger in to get it sorted.)
There we go.
(That's a relief.)
Peanut butter.
He's doing everything that went viral once.
Right. I do everything that is said to be good.
That's good for your health?
It's good for your health.
(His living room table becomes a dining table.)
That's where you always video chat with me, right?
Right.
You two guys video chat with each other?
- Yes. - At around 1am,
Gosh!
we video chat with each other for around two hours...
and talk about acting.
We talk about life as well.
- As if you two were together. - Right.
- Right. - It's fun to talk with him.
(He eats at the place he video chats with Na Ra.)
(Watching)
(Laughing)
(Peeking)
(Chuckling)
- What's going on? - What are you watching?
- Again? - "Infinite Challenge."
- The Bangkok Special. - The Bangkok Special.
(He bursts into laughter helplessly.)
I watched...
all episodes of "Infinite Challenge" several times.
When I was young,
there was a time when "Infinite Challenge..."
was the only show I waited for.
That was when I didn't have any struggles or worries...
and felt very comfortable.
I guess I return to those times when I watch the show.
- You return to those times. - I believe "Infinite Challenge..."
is the best show to me.
I always act out the scenes when I meet my friends.
I always say the lines.
"This isn't bushman bread."
"Just shut your mouth and eat the bread!"
(Just shut your mouth and eat the bread!)
(His favorite line)
(Like this?)
"Hurry up and eat, Jun Ha!"
"I'm full." There's a scene that goes like this.
You memorized all of the lines?
As you watch the show,
there are parts that you never noticed before.
It can also be a certain reaction from someone.
Who was your favorite character?
I love Jung Jun Ha...
- Jun Ha. - and also Jung Hyung Don.
Jun Ha is really funny.
- Well, - You didn't realize it at first.
- when I was young, - Right.
people usually liked Jae Seok or Myung Soo.
- It was either one of them. - Right.
But when I became an adult,
I realized there was one more.
It's like understanding Ko Gil Dong after becoming an adult.
Right.
You understood Jun Ha after becoming an adult.
(Smiling brightly)
He's really enjoying the show.
(Chuckling)
(He bursts into laughter during his meal.)
(Laughing)
(Groaning)
(Gosh, my sides.)
He got a cramp.
(I'm done with my meal.)
(He picks something up from his seat.)
(Supplements)
If I don't place them right by me,
I tend to avoid taking them.
- It's where you can see them. - Right.
- Somewhere close. - The closest place possible.
They have to be placed where you can see them.
- That way... - Everything is within reach.
(Grabbing)
(Drinking water is also placed within his reach.)
(He took care of his meal and supplements in the same spot.)
(Getting up)
(He moves to the bathroom with his tablet PC.)
- He carries it everywhere he goes. - He won't miss a single scene.
We might end up watching a whole episode of the show.
(We might end up watching a whole episode of the show.)
(He applies skin lotion in the bathroom.)
Those are placed where they can be seen as well.
(He watches "Infinite Challenge" even while taking care of his skin.)
(Feeling refreshed)
(Rummaging)
What is that?
(The item Bae Na Ra used often)
- The auricular acupuncture needle. - Right.
That helps reduce swelling.
You must not want to sleep again...
after working so hard to reduce your swelling.
- You will swell up again. - You want to keep your face.
Right. You must not want to sleep again.
Na Ra gives me a lot of those tips.
- I see. - Right.
Hold on. He likes that show that much?
(He watches the show even when leaving the bathroom.)
(He gets changed in his room right away.)
You look great.
Thank you.
(He turns off "Infinite Challenge" that was on the whole time.)
(Opening)
Yes.
(He gets out a new apple cutter.)
The apple cutter?
Are you heading out to cut an apple for someone?
Today's important appointment.
Cutting an apple for someone.
That sounds really important.
The weather is great.
(The weather is great.)
- You like leather jackets, right? - I do.
- Is that so? - I'm the LJF.
- My older brother calls me that. - LJF?
I'm the Leather Jacket Freak.
Even when we went on a trip to Japan,
he went to a vintage shop...
- and bought a jacket right away. - A vintage shop?
- Really? - I only focus on leather jackets.
So he's into leather jackets.
Does it not matter if it's artificial leather?
- I try to avoid artificial leather. - Real leather.
I get upset when someone makes fun of me about it.
I get upset when someone asks if it's artificial leather.
(The LJF takes a taxi.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(He heads somewhere.)
(Past the Han River,)
(the taxi moves further out.)
- Hello? - Why aren't you coming?
What?
I'm sorry. I'm not lying about this.
I have 207m left.
Are you out of your mind? I'm standing here on my own.
If it's 207m,
you know that it's nose distance, right?
It's surely nose distance with your nose.
- His nose is famous. - I'm so sorry.
- Did we plan to meet at 3:30pm? - Is it Chae Soo Bin?
What?
(The two bicker even before they meet each other.)
I'll be there in one minute.
Come and write your name with your bottom.
- Okay. I'm getting off now. - Okay.
- The two seem to be really close. - Right.
- She sounds like a close friend. - Right.
Thank you.
- Have a good day. - Thank you. Goodbye.
(Getting out)
- Goodbye! - Goodbye!
Who could it be?
He looks excited.
Gosh, Ms. Lee!
Mr. Yu!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
- A great pleasure! - Who is it?
Are you walking right now?
It's my friend.
- Actress Lee Yeon. - I see.
- In "Perfect Crown," - Right.
we acted together.
We got really close through that show.
"Juvenile Justice."
As a juvenile offender.
She had an overwhelming presence.
She's three years younger than me.
She sometimes feels like a younger sister...
or an older sister with leadership at other times.
She's a great friend of mine.
- What is this? - It's an apple cutter.
(He gives her the apple cutter as a give first.)
Hold this for me. I'll put it in my bag.
(Thank you.)
Should we walk a bit before we eat?
The Han River is right by here.
Right. There's a trail of cherry blossoms.
Have you heard about it?
When she comes...
Someone else must be coming.
Let's say we got confused with the time of appointment.
We'll say we got that time to go for a walk.
- She's here! - Is she?
(She's here!)
Hey!
Ms. Lee!
Why are there so many Ms. Lees?
(IU)
- Ms. Lee! - IU?
Hey!
- She's here! - Is she?
Ms. Lee!
(The friend to come last)
(IU)
- Ms. Lee! - IU?
IU?
(Lips shaking)
It's IU!
(Is he tearing up?)
(He can't believe his eyes.)
Why did you suddenly become a country bumpkin from Mokpo?
IU is here?
(Brightening up)
We were in "Perfect Crown..."
and we got really close while working with each other.
(Amazed)
Hey!
(IU runs over with a smile.)
Ms. Lee!
I would've gone to a beauty shop as well...
- if you were going to go. - I had something before this.
- I had work before this. - Hold on.
It's my friend, IU.
- That must be great. - Right.
We're a year apart from each other,
so we're basically friends of the same age.
When the three of us met often,
it was around once every 1 or 2 weeks.
(They met each other often.)
The three of them must be a family.
(IU)
We went to Jeju Island for 2 days and 1 night.
- The three of you? - Yes.
They wanted to film a short-form video.
You three must be really close.
(A video for an exciting memory)
(They share the same preferences and sense of humor as well.)
I got mixed up with the time I made a reservation for.
I think we have to go for a walk as we have some time left.
What time is the reservation?
It's around 4:30pm.
- It's 4:30pm? - Let's walk for a bit.
Let's go.
(We have no choice but to walk.)
- What time is it, Yeon? - Right now?
It's just past 3pm right now.
It's 3:06pm.
I didn't actually get mixed up with the time.
Ji Eun is a big homebody.
She doesn't enjoy going for walks as well.
- Really? - Yeon and I...
try to make her walk and exercise.
- You wanted to make her exercise? - Right.
(A white lie for the homebody)
(Su Bin leads the younger ones for a walk.)
The weather is great today.
- It's shining so brightly. - Look how bright it is.
- The sun glitter. - I've never seen it before.
(The sun glitter can be seen from afar.)
Sean must be running right now.
(Sean must be running right now.)
You have to run if you get caught by him.
(Be careful.)
- It's a weekday. - Right.
There aren't many people out even though the weather is great.
This is amazing!
It's so nice.
(Walking)
Forsythias.
Did you get to enjoy the flowers?
- Flowers? - Yes.
Did you enjoy the flowers, Maeng Dal?
What's Maeng Dal?
I was called Maeng Gu at first.
- They said I looked like Maeng Gu. - From where?
- "Crayon Shin-chan?" - The one in "Crayon Shin-chan."
- The one with a runny nose? - Right.
- I can see him! - I can see the resemblance!
- Right. - The one with a runny nose.
- He's right here. - Right.
- Right. - What?
- Right. - Right.
Did you wear that on purpose?
Sorry?
- He wears these occasionally. - Yes, I wear them sometimes.
- Su Bin is there. - Would you like it?
- Why would you give it to me? - No?
I'll take them gratefully.
(I'll take them gratefully.)
Did you get to enjoy the flowers?
- Flowers? - Yes.
Did you enjoy the flowers, Maeng Dal?
I sent you photos.
There's a cherry blossom path at Bulgwangcheon Stream...
in front of my place.
Oh, right. There's Bulgwangcheon Stream in front of your place.
- What about you, Ji Eun? - I'm seeing them now.
- These are probably... - The flowers have bloomed.
These are probably the last cherry blossoms Ji Eun will see this year.
Because she doesn't go out.
By the way, isn't it a little hot to wear a leather jacket now?
- Tell me about it. - No, it's perfect.
- It's perfect. Why? - I mean...
- I think you'll sweat. - Now, people are lightly dressed.
Until which month are you going to wear that?
- July. - Until July?
- Then... - Don't mention it until then.
Okay.
- They bloomed beautifully. - They're so pretty.
(They reached the cherry blossom path while walking pleasantly.)
- Want me to take a photo of you? - Sure.
- Give me your camera. - Okay.
It looks good here, right?
I'll take a nice photo of you.
(Skillful)
Su Bin, make it give off a good vibe. Don't make it weird.
All right. With a good vibe.
(A V sign)
(It's a little lacking.)
(Rolling his tongue)
(Proactively making them smile)
(Laughing)
(Thanks to him, they smile broadly.)
Did you take one? Stop already.
- It has a good vibe, right? - Yes, it does.
- This one looks good. - This one's nice.
This one looks really good.
(He took a photo of his friends as though they were flowers.)
That's a nice photo.
- It has a good vibe, right? - Yes, it does.
- This one looks good. - This one's nice.
This one looks really good. Gosh.
- I did it. - Our legs look really long.
Shall we work out here for a bit?
- Here? - Yes.
- Sure. - Is there a workout you recommend?
A workout to recommend?
We can do this lightly.
But your upper body... So, experts...
- Our upper body? - don't move their upper bodies.
They only move their legs.
Like this.
(Laughing)
Your upper body goes...
Your upper body is moving.
No, it's not. It's like...
- I think you can fix it more. - It should be comfortable.
Look.
(I want to give it a try.)
Don't move your upper body.
My upper body isn't moving, right?
(Rolling)
- My upper body isn't moving, right? - Don't roll your body.
Why would you roll your body?
- You know what? This... - Don't move your upper body.
- Did you enter a competition? - No, in the movie I filmed,
- there's a scene where I do this. - Okay.
I'm really good at this.
- She's really good. - That's how you do it.
She's good.
- Yeon loves working out. - They should move separately.
- Yeon does? - Yes.
She always does marathons.
(Impressed)
Really?
Your upper body and lower body should move separately.
(The two of them work out, following Su Bin's lead.)
(Things are going according to my plan.)
And your chest...
Breathe in, and spread your shoulders.
After relaxing the lat muscles, push it.
But he's...
- Why am I so heavy? - I know.
(They burst into laughter after seeing his demonstration.)
It's not supposed to be this heavy.
Your neck was shaking like this. Is this right?
(Struggling)
While I was doing this...
(Happy)
That equipment was a little hard.
It pumps up my chest.
- Like this... - Capture it well when he shakes.
Okay.
- Your turn. - I don't think I can do this.
- You can do it. - I can?
You suggest working out after demonstrating first.
You're a lot more proactive with your friends.
You're really bright.
When I meet others,
I want them to have fun with me.
- That's what I want. - Right.
So I tend to be like that, but my energy gets drained quickly.
You're someone who shares their energy.
- He is. - That's right.
But everyone smiles for you, no matter what you do.
- You make friends well... - That's not easy to do.
in every project.
Try it. You can do it. You can lift your own weight.
I haven't eaten yet, so...
(Heave-ho)
- Are you serious? - You can't even do one?
- For real? - It's not that heavy.
Oh, my. What's wrong with her?
(Grunting)
I can see why you want her to work out.
- You can't even do one. - This isn't easy.
Why can't you do it?
(Easy)
This is...
You need muscles to live long.
(Wishing for a long life)
Aren't you sweating too much on the philtrum?
- It makes you sweat a lot. - There's dew on your philtrum.
It's so funny.
Let's walk a bit and turn around to come back.
Okay.
Can you do the feet clap?
He listens to you so well.
- I'm hungry. - Me too.
Will the restaurant be open...
- if we go now? - Yes.
We're here.
- No matter how much you work out... - We're eating for real now, right?
- I'm hungry. - Shall we drop by the gym?
(What are you talking about?)
All right. Let's go in.
It's really big, though. Finally.
Do they have tangsuyuk too?
- Of course. - A Chinese restaurant?
- Listen carefully. - Okay.
- Let's listen. - Call me if you want to come here.
He must go there really often.
(The restaurant Su Bin booked in person)
- It must be here. - It's really spacious.
Goodness.
- All right. - Gosh.
- I'm starved. - First...
What dishes will they have?
First, we must have blowfish with chives.
- Blowfish with chives? - Yes.
- Blowfish? - Blowfish with chives...
is their main dish.
We'll order a meal for ourselves.
And let's order whatever dish you want to eat.
You don't have to...
- look at the menu, right? - No.
- I want to have tangsuyuk. - Sounds good.
Tangsuyuk.
- Oh, this is an a la carte. - He's like an older brother.
They do serve it.
Sir.
- We'll have a small size... - Fried blowfish with chives.
- of fried blowfish with chives. - A small size.
- All right. I'll have them ready. - Thank you.
Thank you.
No one I brought here was disappointed with this place.
- No one was disappointed? - No.
You guys came to an incredible place.
It's here already.
- No way. - Nice.
- I'm totally ready to dig in. - Here's your dish.
- All right. - Here you go.
(Su Bin's pick, fried blowfish with chives)
- Oh, it's fried blowfish. - That's right.
I've never seen it.
- Listen carefully. - To what?
It's good with mustard too, but for the first bite,
dip it in salt and pepper only.
- Okay. - It's really good.
With salt and pepper for the first bite.
- Thank you. - That way,
you can taste the blowfish only.
(Scooping a dish for each of them...)
(and giving it to them first)
The older one should eat first.
- No, the younger one should. - No, the older one should.
(That's not right.)
Eat up.
- The eldest... - Should eat first.
How can we eat before you do?
That's right.
(In the end, they eat only after the eldest scoops his food.)
Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
- I think I know how it tastes. - I'm curious.
Dipping it in salt must be perfect.
(The younger ones have a bite the same way.)
The blowfish meat...
- is a little seasoned too, right? - Yes.
It's no joke, right?
(Does it suit their palates?)
- It's so good, right? - It's really good.
(Fortunately, it suits the younger ones' palates.)
- It's really good. - It's so good, right?
Yeon loves fish,
- so this must be her style. - Totally.
You sell fish?
- I rarely eat meat. - She doesn't eat meat much.
"Sell fish?"
(IU can't hear really well.)
(Laughing)
(Taking a glance)
(Turning)
- Is it good? - Yes.
(Always placing the dish on the younger ones' side)
You get why I kept...
- mentioning this place, right? - Yes.
Is the shoot going well?
- "High School Detective?" - Yes.
I'm adjusting myself to it.
(Su Bin is in the middle of filming his next movie.)
You must've gotten really close to them now.
We're slowly getting closer.
As soon as he began filming "High School Detective,"
he drifted out of touch.
That's true.
She must be disappointed.
As soon as I began filming "High School Detective,"
I knew you'd say this.
He did drift out of touch.
He answers our texts late too.
What? Really?
I can tell he's tired from his texts.
That's true.
He'll start not checking our group chat.
Then I'll assume that he went over to their group chat.
I can understand it.
(Already super disappointed)
You guys can't live without me. Is that what you're saying?
Betrayers are to be executed.
(Not us)
- You're going to kill me? - Yes.
You'll be labeled, "Betrayer."
(Backing down instantly)
(Joking)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Tangsuyuk looks good. - That place must be good.
(She takes a piece right away and has a bite.)
It must be so good.
What?
(Eye opening)
- Is it good? - It's so good.
She loves tangsuyuk.
Is that so?
Now you can believe that I know good restaurants, right?
Of course I can.
It's so good.
You feel really good if your friends...
enjoy the food of the restaurant you brought them to.
- That's right. - It feels really good.
Yeon eats so well.
(Exclaiming)
It must be good.
It's so good.
(Feeling proud seeing them eat so well)
You crave noodles now, right?
It'd be perfect...
- if we have carbs now. - That's right.
Yes, that'd be good.
- Sir, please give us our meals. - Yes.
- And a Coke Zero, please. - One Coke Zero?
Yes. Thank you.
(He orders noodles dishes too.)
It's so good. It's crunchy.
(Taking a glance)
Guess where this line is from.
(Random)
(Giving them a quiz in the middle of a meal?)
(Focused)
"You're kidnapped."
Wait!
You can't answer right away?
(Thinking about the answer as though they were used to it)
Was it a really famous movie?
I bet it attracted ten million viewers too.
- What? - Is it a movie quiz?
I'm giving them a movie quiz.
You used to love giving an "Infinite Challenge" quiz too.
Yes, I used to love it.
I feel like I know.
There's a really famous line from this movie.
What is it?
"Would you like a share?"
"Who's taking 50?"
- I got it! - Yes.
"The Roundup!"
Correct.
This is fun.
Next.
I should think of one.
What could there be? Among Korean movies.
Here it comes.
(Oh, right away?)
- Right away? - You thought of it quickly.
"Come on!"
- Isn't that Shin-chan? - Isn't that Shin-chan?
- "Come on!" - "Come on!"
I'll go with another one.
(Get ready.)
"Here I go!"
- What? - What is it?
- You don't know this? - It's from a history movie.
What could it be?
You should imitate the actor a little too.
Yes, you should.
- That was just you. - That was you speaking.
- Give us another part. - Another part.
"Maybe it's not you."
- "Maybe it's not you?" - Yes.
"Maybe..."
- I got it! - What's the answer?
"The King's Warden."
- Correct! - Yes!
- Correct! - It's Park Ji Hoon's line.
You should've given us a more famous line.
Isn't "Here I go" the most famous line?
"How dare you dishonor the Royal Family?"
Show it to us.
- We're the only ones here. - "How dare you..."
(Glaring)
"dishonor the Royal Family?"
He's so cool.
He's different.
- "You're doubting me?" - I got it.
- "Assassination." - Correct.
(Nice!)
- I got it! - I got it!
"Exhuma."
- Correct. - Yes!
- "Exhuma." - Right. There's a line like that.
I got it! "The Handmaiden."
- Correct. - They keep going.
- Correct. - I got it. "Crazy Romance."
- Correct. - They must watch a lot of movies.
They're actors, that's why.
I can tell that the pattern of the conversation...
is one Su Bin has when he's with people he likes.
- For real. - Really?
Have you ever given a quiz to Na Ra too?
- I'd give it when we're on a trip. - That's right.
- The more we talk... - We'd play games a lot.
It's fun, though.
Shall we do one too, Hyun Moo?
- I'll give you a quiz. - Okay.
(Thinking)
(Bring on the movie quiz.)
- "Hey, lady!" - I know!
(I got it!)
- "Tazza: The High Rollers." - That's correct.
- What is that? - He'd wake up from a nap...
- and say, "Hey, lady!" - Oh, Goni does?
- Yes, Goni does. - Oh, it's Goni?
- Yes. People used to say it a lot. - Yes.
Then guess where this is from. It's my favorite movie.
"Gosh, you should stop..."
"trying to establish a rivalry with me."
I got it! It's from "The Unjust."
(Movie, "The Unjust")
- "The Unjust?" - I think he's especially good...
at memorizing.
The actor sat with Hwang Jung Min under a parasol.
It's my all-time favorite movie.
It's...
- What? - I'm supposed to be Yoo Hai Jin.
(Darn it!)
(Shaking)
Jun Hyun Moo in the energy drink commercial.
- Correct! - The horror version.
(Darn it!)
(Shaking)
What is that?
- I got it! - Darn it.
- That's also from "The Unjust." - Correct.
- What? - How were we supposed to get it?
(The master of movie quizzes who can answer it all)
You're quite good.
You didn't hang the Shin-chan keychain today.
- Doesn't it mean we're over? - You didn't hang it, did you?
- You hung the Maeng Dal keychain? - Maeng Dal.
I didn't bring my bag today.
- Then you can't say that to us. - I don't have my bag with me,
so where am I supposed to hang it?
- Ji Eun, you hung it? - She must have.
- No way. - Is it a friendship keychain?
- A friendship keychain? - You brought it? Or...
I hung it.
Yes, if you brought a bag, you should've hung it.
You could've hung it on the loop of your pants.
- The keyring? - That's right.
- You should've hung it on the loop. - Hang it there?
You should've pierced your ear and hung it there.
Or on your tongue, like a tongue piercing.
I was in the wrong. That's right.
They must be disappointed.
I thought we were to carry it around all the time.
(Sullen)
You should reflect on your wrongdoing.
Shall we do a chant like, "Our friendship forever?"
(That's childish.)
- Not so long ago, - Yes?
my mom and dad said they were really grateful for you two.
Because you came to the funeral.
Ji Eun's maternal grandfather passed away.
Only the two of you came...
among my friends.
You guys came right away,
so I was moved too.
When you came,
both of you brought chocolates.
That's right. I heard...
- Really? - that you brought it too.
Maeng Dal...
brought every chocolate flavor...
in a zipper bag.
Because the family members...
- are tired... - Exactly.
- To recharge energy. - It was...
of great help to me.
After that, Yeon came.
- Yeon brought chocolates too. - I see.
That kind of thought can never occur for me.
- Thanks to you guys... - I'm glad to hear that.
After my mom and dad saw Maeng Dal,
they said he was so handsome in real life.
- They said he was really handsome. - Yes.
They said you were really handsome.
He's really happy when I mention this.
I love it.
Everyone was surprised then.
They were like, "He's that guy?"
- He's handsome in person. - He's handsome.
- You're full now, right? - Yes, I'm full.
(Shall we get going since we're done?)
Let's go.
- That was a great meal, sir. - Sure. Thank you.
- Today as well... - Thank you for the food.
The fried blowfish with chives is really...
- The older one is paying. - Thank you.
- It was a great meal. - Thank you for the food.
They're going to call me...
- if they want to come here. - For sure.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you.
I'll come back again soon.
You're like an older brother who takes care of them well.
- Thank you. - I know.
I can afford prices around that range.
If it gets more expensive...
Then who pays?
Ji Eun, of course.
"Of course?"
(Su Bin is taking the younger ones somewhere.)
- Let's go in. - They're going somewhere again?
Sometimes, we take portraits.
Oh, photos?
(Picking the items they like as they're used to it)
It looks like this has always been on my head.
- Look at her. - Look at this.
Isn't she so cute?
(They position themselves inside.)
(Posing skillfully)
(Adding a playful expression)
- Did we get it? - Come to the middle.
(They move busily...)
(and make memories again.)
To get more strength.
(We're done!)
It came out fast.
- It turned out nice. - Yes. It's hip.
- It turned out really nice. - It did.
(They made another memory together.)
(This is fun.)
- Today was... - It was great.
- I'm leaving. - Bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
That was simple.
- That's... - That really was simple.
(Sleeping soundly)
(Shaking)
He must've been really tired.
(Sharing all his energy to his friends)
He passed out.
A tiring day.
Actually, no matter who I meet outside,
I need to rest by myself.
- I must rest after meeting people. - Of course.
That's because you're a caring person.
It's his personality.
It's tiring if you keep...
- That's right. - taking care of younger ones.
Yes.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Gosh, it's pretty.
(Lifting his head)
(Seeing cherry blossoms at night after a sweet nap)
I think cherry blossoms are prettier at night.
- I agree. - I agree.
(He hums.)
(Striding)
- A cafe? - It's a cafe I go to often.
I'll take two glasses...
(I'll take two glasses of beer.)
- of beer. - Two?
- Is it called tuna bread? - Yes.
I'll take one of that.
- Tuna bread. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Yes, thank you.
(He sits himself in the corner.)
(Then he takes out wireless earphones.)
(Putting them in his ears)
Maybe he's watching "Infinite Challenge again."
(Taking it out)
(Playing music instead of "Infinite Challenge")
(He hangs out by himself after hanging out with his friends.)
Yes.
- Here's your beer and bread. - Thank you.
(Gulping it down right away)
(Exclaiming)
(Amazed)
(Taking a big bite of the bread)
(Yes, this is it.)
Nice.
I think I'm definitely the type of person...
who needs alone time after being with people.
So,
when I'm with others, it's really nice,
and I get energy from them,
but when I get home, I collapse and lie stretched out.
It's really lonely,
(Living alone is really lonely, but...)
but I don't want to let go of living alone.
I can totally relate to that feeling.
The good guys are usually like that.
That's right.
I think a lot about how others...
- think. - That's right.
- That's being considerate. - I see.
- That's being considerate. - It's tiring.
That's why your energy is drained.
You definitely need time to recharge by yourself.
(Time filled entirely with yourself)
(What completes the happy day...)
(The Last Piece of the Puzzle)
(Next story)
(They have the desire to run.)
(People with the desire to run)
(A man who wants to awaken that desire)
(Running that's fun, Fun Run)
The distance doesn't matter.
(The history of Fun Run that Moomoo wrote by himself)
(I'm going to make Fun Run Crew one day.)
(The Fun Run that will shake up Korea...)
(is coming.)
(The first step...)
(of the 1st Fun Run Crew)
- Oh, what? - Hi.
(Stumbling)
(The great history begins.)
(Did you put on makeup?)
(Not the president, but makeup)
(Hyun Moo, Dowoon,)
(Na Ra, Ji Hyeon)
(Moo Do Ra Ji)
(The foundation of Moo Do Ra Ji, the 1st Fun Run crew)
(An unavoidable tryout)
(Start!)
(A fierce competition...)
(to join the crew)
(Let's squeeze out all the strength out of me!)
(The certificate of passing given to Do Ra Ji)
I drew your faces.
(A welcome gift filled with his love)
(Their portraits make them laugh.)
(Gosh, this is so bad.)
(What is this?)
(You should have lower eyelid fat repositioning.)
(Affection growing through well wishes)
(We're going to do a whale run...)
(by the East Sea.)
(Do Ra Ji)
(The Birth of the 1st Fun Run Crew, Moo Do Ra Ji)
(Anju is my family...)
(and the brother I love.)
(Shadow, love, and friendship)
(My friend Anju...)
(who's lived with me for 13 years)
(He's a grandpa cat who is already 13 years old.)
(To me, he's still like a baby.)
(To properly make lasting memories,)
(I came to a self photo studio.)
(Shall we take a photo?)
(Anju, I'm a model.)
(A model brother...)
(has a model cat.)
(Cutie)
(Play with me.)
(A game of tag suddenly started.)
(Wait. Sir?)
(Anju, we don't have much time.)
(I'm excited.)
(He's sweating buckets in no time.)
(Was it this hard to take a photo?)
Anju.
(Groggy)
(Full of energy)
I didn't know this was hard.
(Love Isn't for Just Anyone)